Suyash Chitranshi

chitranshi1996@gmail.com

+91 7066628523



https://www.behance.net/chitranshisuyash



https://www.linkedin.com/in/suyashchitranshi/

I'm focused on creating clean and user friendly experience, so that it helps user to reach their desired goals. I like visual designing because it enables me to be creative with colors, typography and focus on intricate details that may create positive effect on designs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Systmes Engineer

September 2019 - February 2022

Infosys Ltd. | https://www.infosys.com/

Worked in Visualization tools such as Microsoft Power BI and Business Intelligence suite such as MSBI.

Graphic Design Intern

June 2018 - June 2019

Bike Street Boys | https://www.bikestreetboys.com/ Contributed as a Graphic Designer, created numerous infographics. Prominent Work is creation of Brand Design

Guidelines.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google UX Design Professional Certificate

April 2021 - November 2021

EDUCATION

ENGINEERING BACHELORS DEGREE

Sinhgad Institute of Technology, Lonavala, Maharashtra

B.E , Computer Engineering

CGPA - 8.28

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE

Delhi Public School, Prayagraj, Uttar Pradesh

84.80%

SKILLS

Design

Wireframing Visual Design Graphic Design

Prototyping User Flows & Mockups Information Architecture

Tools

Figma Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

Adobe XD Adobe Indesign Adobe Premiere Pro

<u>Development</u>

HTML Microsoft Power Bl Python

CSS Microsoft SQL Server Java

Bootstrap Microsoft BI Suite